Ahmed Hussein

Web Developer

Gmail | GitHub | LinkedIn | Giza - Egypt | +201102466073

About

My Name is Ahmed Hussein, I'm a senior student at faculty of computers and artificial intelligence at Cairo university, I'm a Frontend developer (React) with +2 years of experience, and I'm a Backend developer (Node) with +1 year of experience.

Education

Computers and Artificial Intelligence, Cairo university

Experience

Front-end, Instructor at MSP
Front-end, Freelancer
Front-end, Internship at RMS
04/2023 - Present
08/2022 - Present
03/2021 - 07/2021

Projects

Portfolio

This is my portfolio it's included some of my projects, my skills, and my contacts.

Green Market

It's a Market for all green products that you need in your kitchen and for your children.

Architects

Embark on a virtual journey through our website and witness the seamless blend of artistry and functionality that defines our architectural masterpieces.

Clinic

Patients can book their roles before going to the clinic, and they can also know the available specialties and specialized doctors, and they can know the opinions of previous patients.

Travel

This website allows you to book your plan to spend your holiday where you want and discover a lot of countries.

Programming Languages

- C++
- Python

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- JSON
- AJAX
- React
- Tailwind CSS
- Material UI

- Redux Toolkit
- Node JS
- MongoDB
- MySQL